Edwin Way Teale Papers 1981.0009
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series XIII: Photographs, undated, 1860s-1990s
  - Subseries A: Negatives, 1912-1978
    - 120 Film Negatives
      - Beaver Bog, 1956 August (Box 280:, Folder 4657-4658)
      - Silver (18 Years Old), 1956 August (Box 280:, Folder 4659)
      - Crocker Lake (Water Scenes), 1956 August (Box 280:, Folder 4660-4661)
      - Sunset over Cocker Lake, 1956 August (Box 280:, Folder 4662)
      - Spencer Lake Road, 1956 August (Box 280:, Folder 4663)
      - Digger Wasp in Overturned Tree, 1956 August (Box 280:, Folder 4664)
      - Edwin and Nellie on Slidedown Mountain, 1956 August (Box 280:, Folder 4665-4666)
      - Carney Brook, 1956 August (Box 280:, Folder 4667-4668)
      - Misery Stream, Maine, 1956 August (Box 280:, Folder 4669)
      - Crocker Lake (Forest Pictures), 1956 August (Box 280:, Folder 4670-4672)
      - Huntington, MA, 1956 August (Box 280:, Folder 4673)
      - New 88 Holiday Coupe Oldsmobile, 1956 August (Box 280:, Folder 4674)
      - Club Moss, Crocker Lake, 1956 August (Box 280:, Folder 4675-4676)
      - Slidedown Mountain, 1956 August 22 (Box 280:, Folder 4677-4678)
      - Fred Nagler Visit, 1956 August 25 - 26 (Box 280:, Folder 4679-4680)
      - Silver on Nellie's Birthday, 1956 September 13 (Box 280:, Folder 4681)
      - Tuckerton and Cape May, 1956 October (Box 280:, Folder 4682)
      - Seaweed Set (E. Morgan), 1956 October 8 (Box 280:, Folder 4683-4684)
      - N.Y.C. Apartments Where I Lived First, 1956 October 10 (Box 280:, Folder 4685-4686)
      - Edwin with First Page of Autumn Review, 1956 October 14 (Box 280:, Folder 4687)
      - Monterey Jack at Jones Beach, 1956 October 15 (Box 280:, Folder 4688)
      - Done, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4689-4690)
      - Summer Trip, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4691-4796)
      - Summer Trip, Flying Over Rockies, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4697-4698)
      - Summer Trip, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4697-4698)
      - Summer Trip, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4699)
      - Summer Trip, Texas, Oklahoma, Black Mesa, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4700)
      - Summer Trip, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4701)
      - Summer Trip, Edwin and Nellie, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4702)
      - Summer Trip, Rockport, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4703-4704)
      - Summer Trip, Texas Coast, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4705-4706)
      - Summer Trip, Rockport, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4707)
      - Summer Trip, Montana, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4708)
      - Summer Trip, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4709-4710)
      - Summer Trip, Trail Ridge Road, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4711-4712)
      - Summer Trip, Mayflies, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4713-4715)
      - Summer Trip, Mayfly Island, Ohio, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4716-4717)
      - Summer Trip, Peninsula, Michigan, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4718-4724)
      - Summer Trip, Mt. Washington, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4725-4728)
      - Summer Trip, Nebraska, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4729)
      - Summer Trip, Prairie Dogs, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4730-4733)
      - Summer Trip, Great Dunes, Colorado, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4734-4736)
      - Summer Trip, Kansas, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4737)
      - Summer Trip, Rockies, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4738)
      - Summer Trip, Trail Ridge Tundra, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4739-4740)
      - Summer Trip, Mesa Verde, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4741)
      - Summer Trip, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4742)
      - Summer Trip, Silverton, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4743)
      - Summer Trip, Lubbock Prairie Dogs, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4744)
      - Summer Trip, Devil's Lake, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4745-4747)
      - Summer Trip, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4748-4749)
      - Summer Trip, Utah, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4750)
      - Summer Trip, Rockpor, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4751-4753)
      - Summer Trip, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4754-4759)
      - Summer Trip, Iowa, Missouri, Kansas, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4760-4761)
      - Summer Trip, Prairie Dogs, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4762-4764)
      - Summer Trip, Pikes Peak, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4765-4767)
      - Summer Trip, Trail Ridge Road, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4768)
      - Summer Trip, Grand Mesa, 1957 (Box 280:, Folder 4769)
      - Summer Trip, Painted Desert, 1957 (Box 281:, Folder 4770-4771)
      - Summer Trip, Niagra Falls, 1957 (Box 281:, Folder 4772)
      - 35mm - Exacto Test Film, 1957 January 12 (Box 281:, Folder 4773)
      - Christopher Medal, 1957 May (Box 281:, Folder 4774)
      - Earlham - L.L.D., 1957 June (Box 281:, Folder 4775)
      - Edwin 58th Birthday, 1957 June 2 (Box 281:, Folder 4776)
      - Earlham - L.L.D. Trip, 1957 June 7 - 9 (Box 281:, Folder 4777-4779)
      - Done, 1958 (Box 281:, Folder 4780)
      - June Journey, 1958 (Box 281:, Folder 4781-4801)
      - Winter in Yard, 1958 (Box 281:, Folder 4802)
      - Winter Trip, Maine, 1958 (Box 281:, Folder 4803-4084)
      - EWT, Nellie, 1958 Marc (Box 281:, Folder 4805)
      - Tommy Dodd, Putney, VT, 1958 March 15 (Box 281:, Folder 4806)
      - Kierans at Rockport, 1958 March 17 (Box 281:, Folder 4807)
      - Mrs. Roy Newman, Georgetown, Maine, 1958 March 23 (Box 281:, Folder 4808)
      - Untitled, 1958 May (Box 281:, Folder 4809)
      - Low Tide at Tuckerton, 1958 May 19 (Box 281:, Folder 4810)
      - Edwin on 59th Birthday, 1958 June 2 (Box 281:, Folder 4811)
      - Roxbury (Burroughs Country), 1958 July 2 (Box 281:, Folder 4812)
      - Pickerelweed, 1958 July 12 (Box 281:, Folder 4813-4814)
      - Tremex on Maple, 1958 August 4 (Box 281:, Folder 4815)
      - Cape May Trip, 1958 October 3 - 6 (Box 281:, Folder 4816-4819)
      - Done, 1958 November 14 (Box 281:, Folder 4820-4824)
      - Baldwin Home, 1959 (Box 281:, Folder 4825)
      - Hampton, 1959 (Box 281:, Folder 4826)
      - Edwin at 60, Hampton, 1959 (Box 281:, Folder 4827)
      - Scenes and House, Hampton, 1959 (Box 281:, Folder 4828)
      - Hampton, Fungi, 1959 (Box 281:, Folder 4829)
      - Hampton, Wildflowers, 1959 (Box 281:, Folder 4830-4831)
      - Hampton, Insects and Wildlife, 1959 (Box 281:, Folder 4832)
      - Hampton, 1959 (Box 281:, Folder 4833)
      - Hampton Home, 1959 May 1 (Box 281:, Folder 4834-4839)
      - Hampton Place, 1959 May 11 (Box 281:, Folder 4840)
      - Edwin 60th Birthday, 1959 June (Box 281:, Folder 4841-4842)
      - Josephine Newman, Maine Trip, 1959 June 2 (Box 281:, Folder 4843)
      - Sunday River, 1959 June 3 - 4 (Box 281:, Folder 4844)
      - Hampton Farm, 1959 July (Box 281:, Folder 4845)
      - First Stobonar Pictures, 1959 August 4 (Box 281:, Folder 4846)
      - Farida Wiley Visit, Hampton, 1959 September 1 - 4 (Box 281:, Folder 4847)
      - Hampton, 1959 October 8 (Box 281:, Folder 4848)
      - Hampton House, Best, 1959 October 10 (Box 281:, Folder 4849)
      - Hampton House, 1959 October 10 (Box 281:, Folder 4850)
      - People, Hampton, 1959 October (Box 281:, Folder 4851)
      - Hampton House, 1959 October 15 (Box 281:, Folder 4852)
      - Untitled, 1959 November (Box 281:, Folder 4853-4855)
      - Hughes' Monument, 1959 November 20 (Box 281:, Folder 4856-4857)
      - Untitled, 1959 December (Box 281:, Folder 4858-4859)
      - Bob Titts, Flying Squirrel, 1959 December 5 (Box 281:, Folder 4860)
      - Spiral Ring Notebook for Tommy, 1959 December 14 (Box 281:, Folder 4861)
      - Summer, Hampton - Insects and Wildlife, 1959 (Box 281:, Folder 4862)
      - Snow Tracks Around Trailwood, 1960 (Box 281:, Folder 4863)
      - Edwin at 61, Nellie at 60, 1960 June (Box 281:, Folder 4864)
      - Edwin at Trailwoods, 1960 June 2 (Box 281:, Folder 4865)
      - Leaf-Footed Squash Bug (First 35mm), 1960 June 21 (Box 281:, Folder 4866)
      - Miriam Lorrance Visit, 1960 July (Box 281:, Folder 4867)
      - Ferns at Trailwood, 1960 July (Box 281:, Folder 4868)
      - Bird, 35mm, 1960 July (Box 281:, Folder 4869-4870)
      - Fox Den, 1960 July (Box 281:, Folder 4871)
      - Goats Beard, 1960 July (Box 281:, Folder 4872)
      - Gray Tree Toad at Knothole, 1960 July (Box 281:, Folder 4873)
      - Edwin at Trailwood Waterfall, 1960 July (Box 281:, Folder 4874)
      - Trailwood Pictures, 1960 August (Box 281:, Folder 4875)
      - Crocker Lake, 1960 August 10 - 17 (Box 281:, Folder 4876-4878)
      - White-Footed Mouse Nest, 1960 August - September (Box 281:, Folder 4879)
      - Trailwood, 1960 September (Box 281:, Folder 4880)
      - Crocker Lake, 1960 September 10 - 17 (Box 281:, Folder 4881-4882)
      - Dewy Spidersweb and House, 1960 September 22 (Box 281:, Folder 4883)
      - Trailwood Scenes, 1960 October 10 (Box 281:, Folder 4884)
      - Crocker Lake, 1960 August 10 - 17 (Box 281:, Folder 4885)
      - Monterey Jack Cheese Summer Published, 1960 October 15 (Box 281:, Folder 4886)
      - Fox, 1960 November 2 (Box 281:, Folder 4887)
      - Fox Den and Lost Spring, 1960 November - December (Box 281:, Folder 4888-4889)
      - Snow Scenes at Trailwood, 1960 December (Box 281:, Folder 4890)
      - Maine, Winter, 1961 (Box 281:, Folder 4891-4892)
      - Trailwood, 1961 (Box 281:, Folder 4893-4895)
      - Winter, 1961 (Box 281:, Folder 4896)
      - Winter Trip, Lucerne Valley, 1961 (Box 281:, Folder 4897-4898)
      - Winter Trip, Anza-Borrego, 1961 (Box 281:, Folder 4899-4900)
      - Winter Trip, Chuckawalls Mountains, 1961 (Box 281:, Folder 4901)
      - Winter Trip, Anza-Borrego, 1961 (Box 281:, Folder 4902)
      - Trailwood, 1961 (Box 281:, Folder 4903)
      - Winter Trip, The Silver Strand, 1961 (Box 281:, Folder 4904-4905)
      - Winter Trip, Springerville, Hi Jolly, 1961 (Box 281:, Folder 4906)
      - Winter Trip, The Silver Strand, 1961 (Box 281:, Folder 4907)
      - Winter Trip, Anza-Borrego, 1961 (Box 281:, Folder 4908-4909)
      - Winter Scenes (Trailwood and Hampton), 1961 January (Box 281:, Folder 4910-4912)
      - Snow Scenes at Trailwood, 1961 January (Box 281:, Folder 4913-4914)
      - Winter Pictures After Blizzard, 1961 January 5 (Box 281:, Folder 4915)
      - Edwin on Snowshoes, 1961 January 5 (Box 281:, Folder 4916)
      - Winter Scenes at Trailwood, 1961 February (Box 281:, Folder 4917-4918)
      - Scenes Around Jericho, 1961 March 3 (Box 281:, Folder 4919)
      - Rowland Robinson Home, 1961 March 3 (Box 281:, Folder 4920-4921)
      - Scenes on Road to Bethel, VT, 1961 March 4 (Box 281:, Folder 4922)
      - Sugar Bush, Putney, VT, 1961 March 4 (Box 281:, Folder 4923)
      - Beaver at Putney, VT, 1961 March 5 (Box 281:, Folder 4924)
      - Jackman Region in Winter, 1961 March 12 - 13 (Box 281:, Folder 4925)
      - Maine Deeryard, 1961 March 13 (Box 281:, Folder 4926-4927)
      - Snow Weasel (Maine Deeryard), 1961 March 13 (Box 281:, Folder 4928)
      - March Snow at Trailwood, 1961 March 20 (Box 281:, Folder 4929-4940)
      - Nature Pictures, 1961 June (Box 281:, Folder 4941)
      - New Oldsmobile, 1961 June (Box 281:, Folder 4942)
      - To Do, 1961 June (Box 281:, Folder 4943)
      - Spiders, 1961 June (Box 281:, Folder 4944)
      - Winter, 1961 June (Box 281:, Folder 4945-4953)
      - Insects, 1961 June (Box 281:, Folder 4954-4957)
      - Edwin on 62nd Birthday, 1961 June 2 (Box 281:, Folder 4959)
      - Ovenbird Nest, 1961 June 10 (Box 281:, Folder 4960)
      - Edwin at Trailwood, 1961 June 30 (Box 281:, Folder 4961)
      - Winter Car, 1961 July (Box 281:, Folder 4962)
      - Tunnel Webs, Trailwood, 1961 July 2 (Box 281:, Folder 4963)
      - Klots Visit, 1961 July 12 (Box 281:, Folder 4964)
      - Catbirds in Nest, 1961 July 26 (Box 281:, Folder 4965)
      - Brushpile Study, 1961 August 3 (Box 281:, Folder 4966-4967)
      - Spiders, 1961 September (Box 281:, Folder 4968)
      - White-Footed Mouse Dragging Young, 1961 September 14 (Box 281:, Folder 4969)
      - Bench - Glen Brushpile, 1961 October (Box 281:, Folder 4970)
      - Oldest Sugar Maple in Vermont, 1961 October 2 (Box 281:, Folder 4971)
      - Hammock and Mouse, 1961 October 25 (Box 281:, Folder 4972)
      - Hampton Bird Club, 1961 November 4 (Box 281:, Folder 4973)
      - Jaeger, 1961 December 9 - 10 (Box 281:, Folder 4974-4978)
      - Western Trip, 1961-1962 (Box 281:, Folder 4979-4980)
      - Winter Trip, 1961-1962 (Box 281:, Folder 4981-4988)
      - Winter Trip, Death Valley, 1961-1962 (Box 281:, Folder 4989-4991)
      - Winter Trip, 1961-1962 (Box 281:, Folder 4992-4994)
      - Winter, 1961-1962 (Box 281:, Folder 4995-5000)
      - Trailwood, Fall, 1962 (Box 281:, Folder 5001)
      - Winter Trip, 1962 (Box 281:, Folder 5002-5006)
      - Winter Trip, Peltier Ice Storm, 1962 (Box 281:, Folder 5007-5010)
      - Winter Trip, Walden, 1962 (Box 281:, Folder 5011)
      - Winter Trip, Adirondacks, 1962 (Box 281:, Folder 5012-5016)
      - Winter Trip, Snowflake Man, Vermont, 1962 (Box 281:, Folder 5017-5018)
      - Winter Trip, 1962 (Box 281:, Folder 5019-5021)
      - Winter Trip, Saguaro National Monument, 1962 (Box 281:, Folder 5022)
      - Winter Trip, Oregon Pipe Cactus, 1962 (Box 281:, Folder 5023-5024)
      - Winter Trip, White Sands, 1962 (Box 281:, Folder 5025-5030)
      - Winter Trip, Bitter Lake, The Panhandle, 1962 (Box 281:, Folder 5031)
      - Winter Trip, 1962 (Box 281:, Folder 5032-5034)
      - Winter Trip, Grand Canyon, 1962 (Box 281:, Folder 5035)
      - Winter Trip, 1962 (Box 281:, Folder 5036)
      - Winter Trip, Grand Canyon, 1962 (Box 281:, Folder 5036-5042)
      - Winter Trip, White Mountains, 1962 (Box 281:, Folder 5043-5048)
      - Winter Trip, 1962 (Box 281:, Folder 5049)
      - Winter Trip, Rockport, 1962 (Box 281:, Folder 5050-5052)
      - Winter Trip, Big Bend, 1962 (Box 281:, Folder 5053)
      - Winter Trip, Oregon Pipe Cactus, 1962 (Box 281:, Folder 5054-5056)
      - Winter Trip, Putney, 1962 (Box 281:, Folder 5057-5058)
      - Winter Trip, Olney, 1962 (Box 281:, Folder 5059-5060)
      - Winter Trip, Rockport, Texas, 1962 (Box 281:, Folder 5061-5062)
      - Winter Trip, Lower Rio Grande, 1962 (Box 281:, Folder 5063)
      - Winter Trip, Big Bend, 1962 (Box 281:, Folder 5064)
      - Trailwood, 1962 March (Box 281:, Folder 5065)
      - Trailwood, 1962 May (Box 281:, Folder 5066-5067)
      - Edwin on 63rd Birthday, 1962 June 2 (Box 281:, Folder 5068-5069)
      - Edwin at Desk, 1962 June 6 (Box 281:, Folder 5070)
      - Canadian Broadcast Visit, 1962 June 6 (Box 281:, Folder 5071-5072)
      - Hog-Nosed Snake, 1962 June 10 (Box 281:, Folder 5073)
      - Edwin Working on The Thoughts of Thoreau, 1962 June 26 (Box 281:, Folder 5074-5079)
      - Trailwood, 1962 July (Box 281:, Folder 5080)
      - Trailwood, Winter, 1962 August 28 (Box 281:, Folder 5081-5085)
      - Winter, 1962 September (Box 281:, Folder 5086-5087)
      - Trailwood, 1962 October 10 (Box 281:, Folder 5088)
      - Untitled, 1962 November (Box 281:, Folder 5089)
      - Snow Scenes at Trailwood, 1962 November 19 (Box 281:, Folder 5090-5094)
      - Trailwood, Winter, 1962 December 31 (Box 281:, Folder 5095-5096)
      - Edwin and Nellie, 1963 (Box 282:, Folder 5097)
      - Done, 1963 (Box 282:, Folder 5098-5109)
      - Dunes, 1963 (Box 282:, Folder 5110-5122)
      - Trailwood, 1963 (Box 282:, Folder 5123-5127)
      - Winter, 1963 (Box 282:, Folder 5128-5136)
      - Trailwood, Winter, 1963 (Box 282:, Folder 5137-5144)
      - Building the Pond, Trailwood, 1963 June (Box 282:, Folder 5145-5146)
      - Trailwood, 1963 June (Box 282:, Folder 5147-5148)
      - Edwin on 64th Birthday, 1963 June 2 (Box 282:, Folder 5149)
      - Thoreau Meeting, Concord, 1963 July (Box 282:, Folder 5150)
      - Dunes, 1963 August (Box 282:, Folder 5151-5153)
      - Samuel H. Gottecho, 1963 September (Box 282:, Folder 5154)
      - Trailwood, 1963 October (Box 282:, Folder 5155)
      - Done, Spring, 1964 (Box 282:, Folder 5156-5164)
      - Trailwood, Fall and Winter, 1964 (Box 282:, Folder 5165-5166)
      - Trailwood Pond, 1964 (Box 282:, Folder 5167-5169)
      - Trailwood, Summer and Early Fall, 1964 (Box 282:, Folder 5170)
      - Trailwood, Winter, 1964 (Box 282:, Folder 5171-5173)
      - Trailwood, Winter, 1964 January (Box 282:, Folder 5174-5178)
      - Snow Scenes at Trailwood, 1964 January 30 (Box 282:, Folder 5179-5181)
      - Chickadees, 1964 February 16 (Box 282:, Folder 5182-5183)
      - Trailwood Scenes, 1964 February 16 (Box 282:, Folder 5184-5187)
      - Stanley Gula, Witch Hazel Gatherer, 1964 March (Box 282:, Folder 5188-5190)
      - Skunk and Trailwood Scenes, 1964 April (Box 282:, Folder 5191)
      - Frogs and Toads, 1964 May (Box 282:, Folder 5192)
      - Trailwood and Pond, Samuel Gottacho Visit, 1964 May (Box 282:, Folder 5193-5195)
      - Tommy Dodd Visit, 1964 May 15 - 16 (Box 282:, Folder 5196)
      - Nellie, 1964 May 29 (Box 282:, Folder 5197)
      - Pond Life, 1964 June (Box 282:, Folder 5198)
      - Edwin's 65th Birthday, 1964 June 2 (Box 282:, Folder 5199)
      - Nellie and Edwin by the Pond, 1964 June 18 (Box 282:, Folder 5200)
      - Rachel's Rock, Sunset Rock, Cape Newogen, 1964 September 12 (Box 282:, Folder 5201-5202)
      - Eastport, Maine, 1964 September 13 - 14 (Box 282:, Folder 5203)
      - Done, 1964 November (Box 282:, Folder 5204-5209)
      - Trailwood, Winter, 1964 December (Box 282:, Folder 5210-5211)
      - Crocker Lake, 1965 (Box 282:, Folder 5212-5213)
      - To Do, Fall, 1965 (Box 282:, Folder 5214-5220)
      - Trailwood, Summer, 1965 (Box 282:, Folder 5221-5223)
      - Trailwood, 1965 (Box 282:, Folder 5224-5228)
      - Untitled, 1965 (Box 282:, Folder 5229-5238)
      - Winter Book, Jacket, 1965 January 19 (Box 282:, Folder 5239-5240)
      - Tracks in Snow, 1965 February 15 (Box 282:, Folder 5241-5243)
      - Edwin, Winter at Trailwood, 1965 March (Box 282:, Folder 5244-5245)
      - Trailwood Scenes, 1965 June (Box 282:, Folder 5246-5249)
      - Witch Hazel, 1965 July (Box 282:, Folder 5250-5251)
      - Crocker Lake, Maine Vacation, 1965 August 7 - 14 (Box 282:, Folder 5252-5257)
      - Wandering Through Winter, Publication, 1965 September (Box 282:, Folder 5258-5260)
      - Crocker Lake, 1965 September (Box 282:, Folder 5261-5264)
      - Building the Cabin, 1965 September - October (Box 282:, Folder 5265)
      - Lawrence Visit, New York Times Front Page, 1965 October (Box 282:, Folder 5266-5268)
      - Cabin, 1965 October (Box 282:, Folder 5269-5271)
      - "To Tell The Truth", 1965 October (Box 282:, Folder 5272-5274)
      - Britain Trip, Northern England, 1966 (Box 282:, Folder 5275-5284)
      - Britain Trip, Upper Scotland, 1966 (Box 282:, Folder 5285-5289)
      - Britain Trip, Lower Scotland, 1966 (Box 282:, Folder 5290-5294)
      - Britain Trip, Below Midlands, 1966 (Box 282:, Folder 5295-5301)
      - Britain Trip, Southern England, 1966 (Box 282:, Folder 5302-5315)
      - Britain Trip, Below Midlands, 1966 (Box 282:, Folder 5316-5320)
      - Britain Trip, Midlands, 1966 (Box 282:, Folder 5321-5330)
      - Britain Trip, Final Selection, 1966 (Box 282:, Folder 5331-5338)
      - Britain Trip, Midlands, 1966 (Box 282:, Folder 5339)
      - Cabin and Pond in Winter, 1966 February (Box 282:, Folder 5340-5342)
      - Maine Vacation, 1966 September (Box 282:, Folder 5343-5346)
      - Trailwood, Winter, 1966-1967 (Box 282:, Folder 5347)
      - Thoreau Society Meeting, 1967 (Box 282:, Folder 5348)
      - Trailwood, 1967 Summer (Box 282:, Folder 5349-5351)
      - Trailwood, 1967 (Box 282:, Folder 5352-5354)
      - Trailwood, 1967 Winter (Box 282:, Folder 5355)
      - Trailwood, 1967 (Box 282:, Folder 5356)
      - Van Doren Visit, 1967 May 8 - 9 (Box 282:, Folder 5357)
      - Trailwood, 1967 June (Box 282:, Folder 5358)
      - Maine Vacation, 1967 August (Box 282:, Folder 5359-5364)
      - Nellie on 67th Birthday, 1967 September 13 (Box 282:, Folder 5365)
      - Cabin at Trailwood, 1967 September - October (Box 282:, Folder 5366)
      - Trailwood, 1968 (Box 282:, Folder 5367)
      - Trailwood Pictures, 1968 June (Box 282:, Folder 5368)
      - Edwin 69th Birthday, 1968 June 2 (Box 282:, Folder 5369)
      - "Snow White" Last Day and New Oldsmobile, 1968 June 7 (Box 282:, Folder 5370)
      - New Hampshire Vacation, 1968 June 9 (Box 282:, Folder 5371)
      - Thoreau Society Meeting, 1968 July 13 (Box 282:, Folder 5372-5374)
      - New Hampshire, 1968 August (Box 282:, Folder 5375)
      - Crocker Lake, Maine, 1968 August 10 - 17 (Box 282:, Folder 5376-5381)
      - To Do, 1968 August 31 (Box 282:, Folder 5382-5383)
      - Autumn, 1969 (Box 282:, Folder 5384-5387)
      - Trailwood, 1969 Winter and Spring (Box 282:, Folder 5388)
      - Trailwood House in Winter, 1969 (Box 282:, Folder 5389-5390)
      - Trailwood House in Winter and Spring, 1969 (Box 282:, Folder 5391)
      - Trailwood Pictures, 1969 Spring (Box 282:, Folder 5392-5394)
      - Trailwood Pictures, Winter and Spring, 1969 (Box 282:, Folder 5395)
      - Hampton Brook in Flood, 1969 March (Box 282:, Folder 5396-5397)
      - April, Trailwood House in Spring, 1969 (Box 282:, Folder 5398)
      - 70th Birthday Pictures, 1969 June 2 (Box 282:, Folder 5399-5402)
      - Walter Harding on Sudbury, 1969 July 12 (Box 282:, Folder 5403)
      - Crocker Lake, 1969 August (Box 282:, Folder 5404-5406)
      - Final Enlarging, 1969 August - September (Box 282:, Folder 5407-5412)
      - Cedar Waxwing, 1969 September (Box 282:, Folder 5413-5414)
      - Nellie on 69th Birthday, 1969 September 13 (Box 282:, Folder 5415-5417)
      - Trailwood, Pennington Visit, 1969 December (Box 282:, Folder 5418-5419)
      - To Do, 1970 Fall (Box 282:, Folder 5420-5421)
      - Trailwood Pictures, 1970 (Box 283:, Folder 5422)
      - Trailwood, 1970 (Box 283:, Folder 5423-5424)
      - Trailwood, 1970 February (Box 283:, Folder 5425-5426)
      - Rockport, Texas, 1970 April (Box 283:, Folder 5427-5429)
      - The Big Thicket, Texas, 1970 April (Box 283:, Folder 5430-5431)
      - The Dune Country, 1970 May (Box 283:, Folder 5432-5433)
      - Crocker Lake, 1970 August (Box 283:, Folder 5434-5438)
      - Done, 1970 August 20 (Box 283:, Folder 5439-5442)
      - Deacon Mosley's Gravestone, Trailwood, 1970 September (Box 283:, Folder 5443)
      - White Mountains Vacation, 1970 September 11 - 14 (Box 283:, Folder 5444-5446)
      - Monterey Jack Cheese (Publication Day), 1970 September 20 (Box 283:, Folder 5447-5449)
      - Indiana University Degree, 1970 October (Box 283:, Folder 5450)
      - Trailwood and Shelburne Inn, 1970 November 3 - 5 (Box 283:, Folder 5451)
      - Trailwood, 1971 Winter (Box 283:, Folder 5452-5456)
      - John McDonald Visit, 1971 May 29 (Box 283:, Folder 5457)
      - Balloon Trip, 1971 May 29 (Box 283:, Folder 5458)
      - Edwin's 72nd Birthday at Trailwood, 1971 June 2 (Box 283:, Folder 5459-5460)
      - Luna Moth, 1971 June 11 (Box 283:, Folder 5461-5462)
      - Walter Harding Farm, 1971 June - July (Box 283:, Folder 5463-5465)
      - Nellie Portraits, 1971 August (Box 283:, Folder 5466)
      - Crocker Lake, 1971 August (Box 283:, Folder 5467-5471)
      - Gerald Humphery, 1971 September (Box 283:, Folder 5472-5474)
      - Jack and Renee Kimmick Visit, Tommy Dodd, 1971 October (Box 283:, Folder 5475-5476)
      - Old Odds, 1971 November 20 (Box 283:, Folder 5477)
      - Trailwood and Hampton, 1972 Spring (Box 283:, Folder 5478)
      - Trailwood, 1972 Spring (Box 283:, Folder 5479-5483)
      - Nellie and Edwin, 1972 February (Box 283:, Folder 5484-5489)
      - Crocker Lake Vacation, 1972 August (Box 283:, Folder 5490-5499)
      - Walden Pond, 1972 August 30 (Box 283:, Folder 5500)
      - North Cemetery, Hampton, 1972 September (Box 283:, Folder 5501)
      - Pond, 1972 October (Box 283:, Folder 5502-5504)
      - Trailwood House, 1972 October (Box 283:, Folder 5505)
      - Woods - Trails, 1972 October (Box 283:, Folder 5506)
      - Trailwood, 1972 November (Box 283:, Folder 5507)
      - Beaver Pond, 1972 November (Box 283:, Folder 5508-5511)